Campus Action Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Events, 1992-2004; Undated; nam_apap164-3
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Conference List, 2002; nam_apap164-3_31
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Conference Report, 2002; nam_apap164-3_32
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Conference Schedule, 2002; nam_apap164-3_33
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Flyer Email Version, 2002; nam_apap164-3_34
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Instructions For Breakout Group Facilitators, 2002; nam_apap164-3_35
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Panel Introduction Sheet, 2002; nam_apap164-3_36
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Press Release, 2002; nam_apap164-3_37
  - "Becoming Anti-Racist Activists", Conference, Thank You Letter, 2002; nam_apap164-3_38
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, "America, Business As Usual" Image, 2003; nam_apap164-3_39
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, "Breaking The Chains", Image, 2003; nam_apap164-3_40
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, "Breaking The Chains, Bring The War Home", Image, 2002; nam_apap164-3_41
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, Building Strong Organizations Flyer, 2003; nam_apap164-3_42
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, Conference Flyer, 2003; nam_apap164-3_43
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, Conference Schedule, 2003; nam_apap164-3_44
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, Conference Schedule Facilitators, 2003; nam_apap164-3_45
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, "End The Slavery", Image, 2003; nam_apap164-3_46
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, Fall Conference List, 2003; nam_apap164-3_47
  - "Building Strong Organizations", Conference, "Fighting Powers, Grassroots-Capital", Image, 2003; nam_apap164-3_48
  - "Building the Peace Movement", Conference, Conference Email, 2003; nam_apap164-3_49
  - "Building the Peace Movement", Conference, Facilitation Schedule For February 8 Inter, 2003; nam_apap164-3_50
  - "Building the Peace Movement", Conference, Fall Conference List, 2003; nam_apap164-3_51
  - "Building the Peace Movement", Conference, Flyer 2, 2003; nam_apap164-3_52
  - "Building the Peace Movement", Conference, Schedule For Inter-Campus Anti-War Meeting, 2003; nam_apap164-3_53
  - "Student Organization Strategies", Conference, Conference Flyer, 2002; nam_apap164-3_54
  - "Student Organization Strategies", Conference, Conference List, 2002; nam_apap164-3_55
  - "Student Organization Strategies", Conference, Conference Schedule, 2002; nam_apap164-3_56
  - "Student Organization Strategies", Conference, Conference Schedule Facilitators, 2002; nam_apap164-3_57
  - "Student Organization Strategies", Conference, Erica's Letter, 2002; nam_apap164-3_58
  - "Take The Power Back", Conference, Attendees Fall Conference, 2001; nam_apap164-3_59
  - "Take The Power Back", Conference, Campus Schedule -- Weekends Good For Conference, 2002; nam_apap164-3_60
  - "Take The Power Back", Conference, Flyer, 2001; nam_apap164-3_61
  - "Take The Power Back", Conference, Follow-up Letter, 2001; nam_apap164-3_62
  - "Take The Power Back", Conference, Schedule, 2001; nam_apap164-3_63
  - "Uniting To Challenge Racism", Conference, Conference Flyer, 2003; nam_apap164-3_64
  - "Uniting To Challenge Racism", Conference, Conference Schedule, 2004; nam_apap164-3_65
  - "Uniting To Challenge Racism", Conference, Email Recruiting Invitation, 2004; nam_apap164-3_66
  - "Uniting To Challenge Racism", Conference, Panel Introduction Sheet, 2004; nam_apap164-3_67
  - "Uniting To Challenge Racism", Conference, Racism Conference Email, 2004; nam_apap164-3_68
- Subject Files, 1993-2003; Undated; nam_apap164-4
  Arranged by topic.
  The materials in this series relate to issues of interest to Campus Action. These files contain collected publications, news clippings, articles, fliers, webpages, correspondence, and other materials related to the individual topics of interest. Particularly well documented in the paper records of Campus Action is the issue of date rape on university campuses. Campus Action's opposition to the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq is particularly well documented in the electronic records, with related defenses of detainees in the civil rights and racism sections. Represented here are also materials created by other campus groups that worked with Campus Action including the Black and Latino Network; Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network; and the NETWORK student organization. The case of Ali Yaghi is also documented in the electronic records. Yaghi, an Albany resident and owner of a pizza shop, was arrested just days after 9/11. He was detained on the basis of a tip by a passerby, who claimed to have heard Yaghi making anti-American statements. Yaghi was detained for months and though eventually cleared of all allegations related to terrorism, he was deported to his native Jordan because of his immigration status.
  - Environment, Correspondence, 1997-1998; nam_apap164-4_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Feminism, National Organization for Women, Publications List, Undated; nam_apap164-4_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights, Kensington Welfare Rights Union, Article, 1998; nam_apap164-4_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Internships, 1993-1995; Undated; nam_apap164-4_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Judicial Decisions, News Clippings, 1996-1997; nam_apap164-4_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian and Gay, AIDS Quilt, 1998; nam_apap164-4_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Correspondence, 1998; nam_apap164-4_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Equality Begins At Home Campaign, Fliers, Contact List, 1989; nam_apap164-4_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Gay, Lesbian And Straight Education Network (GLSEN), 2001; Undated; nam_apap164-4_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Lesbian, Gay, And Bisexual Alliance, 1994; 1996; nam_apap164-4_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Peer Education, Articles, Correspondence, 1998; nam_apap164-4_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride Agenda, 1998; nam_apap164-4_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride Alliance Network, Correspondence, 2005; nam_apap164-4_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride Connection, Contact Lists, 1997-1998; 2001-2002; Undated; nam_apap164-4_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Queer Network, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Resources, 1998; 2001; Undated; nam_apap164-4_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lesbian and Gay, Status of Key Bills, 1997-1998; nam_apap164-4_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lesbian and Gay, "Understanding the Issues Facing Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgendered Survivors of Sexual Assault Who Struggle with Mental Illness, Resource Packet, 1998; nam_apap164-4_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Organizing College Campuses Against Dating Abuse", National Resource Center on Domestic Violence, 1999; nam_apap164-4_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peace Internship, Notes, Flier, Undated; nam_apap164-4_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Racism, Anti-Racism Task Force, 1998-1999; 2002; Undated; nam_apap164-4_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Racism, Articles, News Clippings, 1997-1998; nam_apap164-4_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Racism, Black and Latino Network, 1993-1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Racism, Mock Trial, News Clippings, Biographical Material, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Racism, Moore Case, Correspondence, News Clippings, Petition, 1997; nam_apap164-4_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Racism, Rally Against Racism, 1996; nam_apap164-4_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Sexual Aggression and Acquaintance Rape: A Survey of Union College Students", Undated; nam_apap164-4_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Sexual Assault, Acquaintance Rape, Fliers, Handouts, Undated; nam_apap164-4_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sexual Assault, Articles, News Clippings, 1993-1996; nam_apap164-4_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sexual Assault, Contact Lists, 1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sexual Assault, Correspondence, 1994-1995; 1998; 2002-2003; Undated; nam_apap164-4_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sexual Assault, Drugs, Press Releases, Fliers, 1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sexual Assault, Economic Costs of Sexual Violence, Articles, 1995-1996; nam_apap164-4_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sexual Assault, Educational Material, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Sexual Assault, Faculty Response, 1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sexual Assault, Feminists United For Action, 2002; Undated; nam_apap164-4_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sexual Assault, Fliers, Leaflets, Pamphlets, 1994-1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Sexual Assault, Harassment Log, Undated; nam_apap164-4_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Sexual Assault, Inter-campus Sexual Assault Task Force, 1996-1999; nam_apap164-4_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sexual Assault, Inter-campus Sexual Assault Task Force, 2005; Undated; nam_apap164-4_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sexual Assault, Lobby Day, Fliers, Mailings, 1996; nam_apap164-4_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sexual Assault, Media Resources, 1994; 1996; Undated; nam_apap164-4_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sexual Assault, Middle Earth Peer Assistance Program, 1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Sexual Assault, Model Policies, 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Sexual Assault, National Organization for Women, Fliers, Undated; nam_apap164-4_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Sexual Assault, Nature of Consent, Undated; nam_apap164-4_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Sexual Assault, NETWORK Student Group, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Sexual Assault, Notes, Undated; nam_apap164-4_48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Sexual Assault, Penal Code, Undated; nam_apap164-4_49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Sexual Assault, Policies from Other Campuses, 1996-1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Sexual Assault, President's Task Force for Women's Safety, 1997-1998; nam_apap164-4_51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Sexual Assault, Rape Crisis Center, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Sexual Assault, Resources, 1992-1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Sexual Assault, Role of Men, 1996; 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Sexual Assault, Sexual Assault Reform Act, Legislation, 1997; nam_apap164-4_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Sexual Assault, Sexual Harassment, 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_56 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Sexual Assault, Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Fliers, Undated; nam_apap164-4_57 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Sexual Assault, Siena Work Club, Correspondence, Undated; nam_apap164-4_58 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Sexual Assault, Stalking, Article, 1997; nam_apap164-4_59 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Sexual Assault, Statistics, 1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_60 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Sexual Assault, Student Contacts, 1996-1998; Undated; nam_apap164-4_61 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Sexual Assault, Surveys, 1996; Undated; nam_apap164-4_62 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Sexual Assault, Survivor Resources, 1996; Undated; nam_apap164-4_63 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Sexual Assault, United Council Campus Safety Awareness Manual, 1997; nam_apap164-4_64 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Sexual Assault, University at Albany Publications, 1997; Undated; nam_apap164-4_65 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Sexual Assault, Violence Against Women Prevention Act, Summary, 1998; nam_apap164-4_66 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Sexual Assault, Whistlewatch Program, Undated; nam_apap164-4_67 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Civil Liberties, Ansar Mamood Petition, 2004; nam_apap164-4_68
  - Civil Liberties, Artists for Social Justice Concert, 2003; nam_apap164-4_69
  - Civil Liberties, Defense Committee Contacts, 2004; nam_apap164-4_70
  - Civil Liberties, Draft Brochure, 2004; nam_apap164-4_71
  - Civil Liberties, Draft Panel Letter, 2004; nam_apap164-4_72
  - Civil Liberties, Panel Flyer, 2004; nam_apap164-4_73
  - Civil Liberties, Shokriea Letter, 2003; nam_apap164-4_74
  - Civil Liberties, The Case of Mumia Abu, 2004; nam_apap164-4_75
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Ali Yaghi Paragraph, 2004; nam_apap164-4_76
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Ali Yaghi Sample Letters, 2004; nam_apap164-4_77
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Background, 2004; nam_apap164-4_78
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Contributions, 2004; nam_apap164-4_79
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, How You Can Help, 2004; nam_apap164-4_80
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Index, 2004; nam_apap164-4_81
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Links, 2004; nam_apap164-4_82
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Prison Abuse Article, 2004; nam_apap164-4_83
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Write Letters, 2004; nam_apap164-4_84
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Yaghi Family Photograph, 2004; nam_apap164-4_85
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Yaghi Family Story, 2004; nam_apap164-4_86
  - Civil Liberties, Yaghi Family Support Committee, Story By Marty, 2004; nam_apap164-4_87
  - Environmental, Earth Day Lobby Day, 2004; nam_apap164-4_88
  - Environmental, Ecologic General Flyer, 2002; nam_apap164-4_89
  - Environmental, Ecopledge Petition, 2002; nam_apap164-4_90
  - Environmental, Environmental Action Ideas, 2002; nam_apap164-4_91
  - Environmental, Environmental Organizations, 2002; nam_apap164-4_92
  - Environmental, Rain Forest Letter, McNulty, 2001; nam_apap164-4_93
  - Environmental, Rain Forest Letter, Sweeney, 2001; nam_apap164-4_94
  - Feminist Network, Action Ideas, 2002; nam_apap164-4_95
  - Feminist Network, Campus Feminist List, 2003; nam_apap164-4_96
  - Feminist Network, FAN Flier, 2003; nam_apap164-4_97
  - Feminist Network, Feminist Network List, 2002; nam_apap164-4_98
  - Feminist Network, March For Freedom Of Choice, April 25th March Logo, 2003; nam_apap164-4_99
  - Feminist Network, March For Freedom Of Choice, Protecting A Woman, 2004; nam_apap164-4_100
  - Feminist Network, Sexual Assault Taskforce, Campaign Against Sexual Assault, 2002; nam_apap164-4_101
  - Feminist Network, Sexual Assault Taskforce, Model Policies, 2002; nam_apap164-4_102
  - Feminist Network, SUNY Feminist Constitution, 2002; nam_apap164-4_103
  - Feminist Network, Use The F Word, 2002; nam_apap164-4_104
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Bush Agenda Webpage, 2003; nam_apap164-4_105
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Bush Column SUNY, 2003; nam_apap164-4_106
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Emergency Contraceptive Pill Column, 2003; nam_apap164-4_107
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Emergency Contraception Teach-in Webpage, 2003; nam_apap164-4_108
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Emergency Room Emergency Contraception Webpage, 2003; nam_apap164-4_109
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Flyer SUNY, 2003; nam_apap164-4_110
  - Feminist Network, Vox, GAP Flyers, 2003; nam_apap164-4_111
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Timely Access Webpage, 2003; nam_apap164-4_112
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Vox Accomplishments, 2003; nam_apap164-4_113
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Vox Column SUNY, 2003; nam_apap164-4_114
  - Feminist Network, Vox, Web Material, 2003; nam_apap164-4_115
  - Internships, Alternative Internship Directory, 2001; nam_apap164-4_116
  - Internships, Campus Action Intern Sheet, 2002; nam_apap164-4_117
  - Internships, Campus Action Interns Fall 2003, nam_apap164-4_118
  - Internships, Campus Action Labor Intern Proposal, 2002; nam_apap164-4_119
  - Internships, Democracy Matters, Coordinator Job Description, 2001; nam_apap164-4_120
  - Internships, Democracy Matters, Democracy Matters Intern Ad, 2002; nam_apap164-4_121
  - Internships, Democracy Matters, Response To New Intern Inquiry, 2001; nam_apap164-4_122
  - Internships, Elk Intern Contract, 2004; nam_apap164-4_123
  - Internships, Feminist Organizing Internship Available, 2002; nam_apap164-4_124
  - Internships, Intern Interview Questions, 2003; nam_apap164-4_125
  - Internships, Internships Available, 2003; nam_apap164-4_126
  - Internships, Peace Intern Letter, 2003; nam_apap164-4_127
  - Internships, Peace Intern Program Brochure, 2003; nam_apap164-4_128
  - Internships, Peace Intern Recruitment Flyer, 2002; nam_apap164-4_129
  - Iraq, Iraq Campus Organizing Guide, 2001; nam_apap164-4_130
  - Iraq, Iraq Speaker Available, 2003; nam_apap164-4_131
  - Iraq, 2004 March 19; nam_apap164-4_132
  - Iraq, SUNY Flyer, 2003; nam_apap164-4_133
  - Korea, Korea Talking Points, 2003; nam_apap164-4_134
  - Korea, KSN FAQ, 2003; nam_apap164-4_135
  - Korea, Taskforce, 2003; nam_apap164-4_136
  - Labor, Labor Intern Proposal, 2003; nam_apap164-4_137
  - Labor, Take The Pledge, 2003; nam_apap164-4_138
  - Labor, The Miami Model -- FTAA, 2003; nam_apap164-4_139
  - Labor, Trading Freedom, 2003; nam_apap164-4_140
  - Lesbian and Gay, Activist Programs, 2003; nam_apap164-4_141
  - Lesbian and Gay, Activist SRF, 2003; nam_apap164-4_142
  - Lesbian and Gay, Article For Paper, 2003; nam_apap164-4_143
  - Lesbian and Gay, Audre Lord Project Open Letter, 2003; nam_apap164-4_144
  - Lesbian and Gay, Campus Pride Groups, 2003; nam_apap164-4_145
  - Lesbian and Gay, First Meeting Agenda, 2003; nam_apap164-4_146
  - Lesbian and Gay, GLSEN Organizing Guide, 2003; nam_apap164-4_147
  - Lesbian and Gay, Happy Pins, 2003; nam_apap164-4_148
  - Lesbian and Gay, Institutional Review Board (IRB), 2003; nam_apap164-4_149
  - Lesbian and Gay, Learning Contract, 2003; nam_apap164-4_150
  - Lesbian and Gay, Newsletter, September Pride, 2003; nam_apap164-4_151
  - Lesbian and Gay, Paper 6, 2003; nam_apap164-4_152
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride and Diversity Group, 2003; nam_apap164-4_153
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride and Diversity Sign, 2003; nam_apap164-4_154
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride and Diversity Sign 2, 2003; nam_apap164-4_155
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride and Diversity Survey, 2003; nam_apap164-4_156
  - Lesbian and Gay, Pride List, 2001; nam_apap164-4_157
  - Organizing Tips, Act On Convictions, 2001; nam_apap164-4_158
  - Organizing Tips, Action Ideas, Action Ideas For Environmentalists, 2002; nam_apap164-4_159
  - Organizing Tips, Action Ideas, Action Ideas To Create Clean, 2002; nam_apap164-4_160
  - Organizing Tips, Action Ideas, Campaign Against Sexual Assault, 2002; nam_apap164-4_161
  - Organizing Tips, Action Ideas, Challenge Homophobia, 2002; nam_apap164-4_162
  - Organizing Tips, Action Ideas, Fight Racism, 2002; nam_apap164-4_163
  - Organizing Tips, Ant Oppression Tips, 2003; nam_apap164-4_164
  - Organizing Tips, Anti(ist) Strategies, 2003; nam_apap164-4_165
  - Organizing Tips, Building A Campaign Questions, 2001; nam_apap164-4_166
  - Organizing Tips, Building Diverse Coalitions, 2001; nam_apap164-4_167
  - Organizing Tips, Faculty Advisors Role, 2003; nam_apap164-4_168
  - Organizing Tips, How To Organize A Campaign, 2002; nam_apap164-4_169
  - Organizing Tips, How To Plan A Demonstration, 2001; nam_apap164-4_170
  - Organizing Tips, List Of Demands From A Gender Liberation Conference, 2003; nam_apap164-4_171
  - Organizing Tips, Overcoming Apathy, 2003; nam_apap164-4_172
  - Organizing Tips, Rainforest Action Network Student Organizing Handbook, 2004; nam_apap164-4_173
  - Organizing Tips, Tools For White Guys Who Are Working For Social Change, 2003; nam_apap164-4_174
  - Peace, "1 Weekend A Month, My Ass" Flyer, 2004; nam_apap164-4_175
  - Peace, 2005 Military Budget, 2004; nam_apap164-4_176
  - Peace, Action Ideas For Peace Activists, 2002; nam_apap164-4_177
  - Peace, April 20th March, Answer April 20th Flier, 2002; nam_apap164-4_178
  - Peace, April 20th March, April 20th Flier 2, 2002; nam_apap164-4_179
  - Peace, April 20th March, April 20th Call To Action, 2002; nam_apap164-4_180
  - Peace, April 20th March, April March On Washington Unity Statement From The, Undated; nam_apap164-4_181
  - Peace, April 20th March, Capital District Organizing For April 20th Flyer, 2002; nam_apap164-4_182
  - Peace, April 20th March, Email March info, 2002; nam_apap164-4_183
  - Peace, April 20th March, March On Washington April 20th, 2002; nam_apap164-4_184
  - Peace, April 20th March, UPI Story, 2002; nam_apap164-4_185
  - Peace, Articles, Bush's Regime Change Plan For Iraq, 2002; nam_apap164-4_186
  - Peace, Articles, Compliant Press, 2002; nam_apap164-4_187
  - Peace, Articles, Ex-UN Against War, 2002; nam_apap164-4_188
  - Peace, Articles, Gulf Veterans Oppose, 2002; nam_apap164-4_189
  - Peace, Articles, Inspect, 2002; nam_apap164-4_190
  - Peace, Articles, Iraq And Oil, 2002; nam_apap164-4_191
  - Peace, Articles, Iraq Talking Points, 2002; nam_apap164-4_192
  - Peace, Articles, Letter From Baghdad, 2003; nam_apap164-4_193
  - Peace, Articles, Middle East, 2002; nam_apap164-4_194
  - Peace, Articles, NION New York, 2002; nam_apap164-4_195
  - Peace, Articles, NOAH and 9-11 NY Times, 2002; nam_apap164-4_196
  - Peace, Articles, Shaky Legal Grounds, 2002; nam_apap164-4_197
  - Peace, Articles, Talking Points - Why We Oppose, 2002; nam_apap164-4_198
  - Peace, Articles, The Case Against War, 2002; nam_apap164-4_199
  - Peace, Articles, Why U.S. Shouldn't Invade Iraq, 2002; nam_apap164-4_200
  - Peace, Background Info On The Campaign For A New Foreign Policy, 2004; nam_apap164-4_201
  - Peace, Before You Enlist, 2003; nam_apap164-4_202
  - Peace, Call To Action, 2003; nam_apap164-4_203
  - Peace, Campaign Strategy, 2003; nam_apap164-4_204
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, Action Ideas For Anti-War Work, 2003; nam_apap164-4_205
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, Anti-War Network Email List 2, 2003; nam_apap164-4_206
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, High School Student Peace Activists In The Capital District, 2003; nam_apap164-4_207
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, March 1st Meeting Flier, 2003; nam_apap164-4_208
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, Our Plan To Work Together, 2003; nam_apap164-4_209
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, Reasons People Give For Supporting A Wan In Iraq, 2003; nam_apap164-4_210
  - Peace, Campus Action Anti-War Network, Reasons To Oppose War On Iraq, 2003; nam_apap164-4_211
  - Peace, Campus Peace Contacts, 2002; nam_apap164-4_212
  - Peace, Challenging ROTC Proposal, 2003; nam_apap164-4_213
  - Peace, Corrected Letter, 2003; nam_apap164-4_214
  - Peace, Countdown To Kickout SPAN, 2003; nam_apap164-4_215
  - Peace, Counter Recruitment Expert Oskar Castro, 2004; nam_apap164-4_216
  - Peace, Endorsements Of The Campaign For A New Foreign Policy By Albany, 2004; nam_apap164-4_217
  - Peace, February, 15th, March 19th & 20th Text, 2004; nam_apap164-4_218
  - Peace, FBI Memo Spying On The Peace Movement, 2004; nam_apap164-4_219
  - Peace, February, 15th, March 19th & 20th Minutes, 2004; nam_apap164-4_220
  - Peace, Flyer 1, 2003; nam_apap164-4_221
  - Peace, Gore Vidal, 2003; nam_apap164-4_222
  - Peace, Intro Email, 2003; nam_apap164-4_223
  - Peace, Iraq Pledge Of Resistance Legal, 2003; nam_apap164-4_224
  - Peace, March 19th Siena Gonyo, 2004; nam_apap164-4_225
  - Peace, March 20th NYC Demo, Bus Letter, 2004; nam_apap164-4_226
  - Peace, March 20th NYC Demo, Bus Update, 2004; nam_apap164-4_227
  - Peace, March 20th NYC Demo, Endorsers For, 2004 March 20; nam_apap164-4_228
  - Peace, March 20th NYC Demo, Flier Major Protest In New York City, 2004 March 20; nam_apap164-4_229
  - Peace, Military Counter, 2004; nam_apap164-4_230
  - Peace, More Links, 2003; nam_apap164-4_231
  - Peace, No Child Left Behind Letter, 2003; nam_apap164-4_232
  - Peace, November 15th Phone List, 2004; nam_apap164-4_233
  - Peace, NY Times Article On FBI Spying, 2004; nam_apap164-4_234
  - Peace, October 25th Rally, Intro Email, 2003; nam_apap164-4_235